One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Until I can reach the sky,
I believe, until the next tomorrow, hey
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring.
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style.
It begins, it expands, this flavor that exceeds imagination
I feel so good throughout my body, I will become free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far.
Share the one dream, by telling each other.
Share the good times and laugh.
I'll keep going until I can reach the sky.
Let's overcome it now, I believe in the next tomorrow yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall.
I'll be there soon, I believe in one world yeah yeah...
No One Can Stop This Now
What is the matter with me?
I do not wish to refuse Luffy's request...
So I said I would answer the summons...
Even so, I do not feel bad about it!
That is love!
The pain of yearning for the one whom you cannot see will weaken you until you die...
The previous empresses all fell in love,
yet as empresses, they had no choice but to
repress their feelings and remain on the island.
The pain from their suppressed feelings began to hurt them,
and eventually claimed their lives.
However, your decision to go with that man will save your life!
By answering the summons and
maintaining your position as a Warlord,
you will ensure the country's safety,
as well as help Monkey D. Luffy.
I wonder, what star was that man born under?
Usually, any pirate who wants to go to the prison has to turn himself in...
Amazon Lily
Port
Wasn't he setting off tomorrow morning?
It seems that their destination changed.
Seems like he's going to Central with Snake Princess!
Luffy!
You guys! I owe you so much for this...
Next time, I'll bring my friends here too!
Come to think of it, will that be alright?
Nami and Robin should be fine, but men aren't allowed in this country...
If they're your friends, then I think it would be fine.
It seems like this is the saga of "The Snake Princess Made a Special Exception For You", after all.
I'll be looking forward to it!
The saga of "So, You Were Here"?
Who would be so insolent...
as to leave...
a puppy and...
a baby seal blocking my path?!
Snake Princess!
Her sexy pranks know no bounds!!
I don't know when it happened, but she's even more beautiful than before!
I'm so sorry! It was all my fault...
Please be more careful.
I'm sorry that we gotta leave so suddenly.
Snake-woman! I wanna get going as soon as possible!
Oh, no! If I look into his eyes...
No, Luffy! It's rude of you to call her that!
You must address her as "Snake Princess"!
Please, call me Hancock.
Snake Princess!
Yeah, sure thing, Hammock!
It's "Hancock".
S-Snake Princess is smiling!
How many carats? How many carats was that smile?!
Too bright...
A woman in love...
I was like that once...
Huh? Elder Nyon, your face looks all distorted and ugly...
Silence!
Have a safe journey, Snake Princess!
Please come again, Luffy!
Luffy-chan!
See ya la'der!
Stop that already!
I told you my conditions on the Snail-Phone.
If this is about your request to make a stop at the Great Prison, Impel Down,
then I've managed to get permission from above.
Pirates, especially the Seven Warlords, are forbidden to approach the prison.
Only you and that snake will be coming, correct?
This is a special case.
There's no time, so you won't be able to stay there for long.
Then, Big Sister, please be careful.
Make sure you come back alive, Big Sister.
We will pray for your safety, Snake Princess!
Take care, Snake Princess!
Luffy, you take care t-
I will be going, then.
I leave the kingdom to you for the time being.
Yes!
The wait was worth it.
Now, it seems I'll be able to fulfill my mission.
First, could you do something about my petrified crew?
Are they all dead?
Awaken.
...ck-sama!
...What?
Get the ship moving, fools!
Uh, yes! Right away!
Before we go to Marineford, we head for Impel Down!
Navy Headquarters
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
We've gotten a message from Vice Admiral Momonga!
Apparently, the Pirate Empress Boa Hancock
finally responded and is on her way here!
Finally. I sure hope she makes it in time.
That woman is strong.
Now we have six of the Seven Warlords gathered.
What about the last one, still sitting in prison?
Has he come to his senses?
No, he's still completely against this fight.
It seems he's even ready to accept losing his position as a Warlord.
I thought he'd be our strongest supporter in this case...
To think that he'd be this opposed to it...
Damn that Jinbei...
Reporting in!
Fleet Admiral!
It's about those 500 pirates that Admiral Kizaru captured on Sabaody Archipelago...
Impel Down says they don't have the manpower to handle them all...
Talk to the Labor Department!
Don't ask me for anything unrelated to the Whitebeard case!
Oh, and the World Noble, Saint Rosward demands...
Let the Admirals deal with him!
What about Garp?
Vice-Admiral Garp has gone to Impel Down.
What does he think he's doing?!
Doing whatever he pleases at such a crucial moment...
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
This is an emergency!
Whitebeard has made his move!
So, he's coming... the patrol ships reported it?
Patch me through so they can confirm it themselves.
Well, you see...
All 23 ships we had keeping an eye on
Whitebeard's flagship, the Moby Dick...
just vanished. We can't contact them.
W-What?!
Apparently, there have been suspicious movements among other pirates in the New World as well!
We can't get any information on how many of them there are or when they will come here!
We sent out another patrol, but...
He got us!
He's already started to move, hasn't he?
We have no idea where he'll strike...
As long as we've got Ace imprisoned...
We need to tell everyone that it is possible that there might be a showdown in Impel Down!
Yessir!
Great Prison
Impel Down
This way, Vice-Admiral Garp.
Take care!
Sure.
Well, you sure look pitiful...
You still alive there...
Ace?
Old man...
And now, we will travel back in time a little...
Oh dear, oh dear...
Hey...hey...hey...young lady?
Where did you come from, young lady?
Quit repeating yourself.
What is it?
Have you calmed down?
You're not gonna attack me any more, are you?
Ta-dah!
Now, have a look...
at these firmly tied "knots of wind"!
Untie one and...
...it summons a gentle breeze.
Untie another, and...
...it summons a strong wind.
Untie the third, and...
...it summons a storm!
What are you doing?!
I thought it would cheer you up...
I feel better now, thank you very much!
This is Weatheria, a small Sky-Island.
It's a country dedicated to researching weather.
S-Sky-Island?!
Grand Line "Winter Island"
Wait!
Stop it, Taroimo!
It's a human!
Um, are you alright?
He mistook you for a monster...
Yeah, I'm fine.
How can you be alright?!
Still, this is bad...
How far did I fly?
Ugh, it's cold! Is this a snow-country?!
Franky!
This is bad!
He's walking around in the snow wearing only a speedo!
Did someone rob him?
Here, put on this loincloth.
Loincloth?! Get real!
Mind your own business!
If I'd...
...put that on...
...I'd be a disgrace...
...to all perverts!
Follow along!
Move your butt to the right!
Right hand on the hips...
...and thrust your left hand out!
Slide...
...to the left!
Right! Left!
And again!
Yeah!
One! Two!
Super!
Whew, this is the best!
I'm still cold!
Where is this?!
Huh?
This is Mechanical Island's future kingdom of Bulgemore.
The kingdom where geniuses are born.
This is the Island of Dreams in the Grand Line...
Peachy Island.
This is the island known as the second Island of Women.
Everything from the trees to the sea is purely pink.
The humans and animals gathered on this island...
...all possess maiden hearts.
What kind of heaven is this?!
Wait up~!
You're like us!
You are, right?!
Shut up! Don't follow me!
I keep telling you, I'm not!
To my dear Nami-san and Robin-chan...
Are you doing well?
Wait! Wait!
Wait up, dammit!
No way I'd wait!!
Welcome to the Kamabakka kingdom!
Right now...
I'm in Hell.
These islands, blossoming in the sea like flowers, are called the Bowin Islands.
How are you doing?
You're doing too well, dammit!
You gonna eat this?
No way!
But still, you saved me. Thanks!
I don't know who you are, but...
My name is Heracles'un!
Wow, that's a really cool name.
You think'un?
I'm Usopp. Nice to meet you.
Is this edible?
I've never seen a fruit like this before.
It's alright'un, Usopp'un.
And...My name is...
Heracles'un!
I got it. You're cool.
It sure smells good...
I'll just give it a lick...
Usopp'un!
W-What was that?!
Was that thing trying to eat me?!
Of cours'un. It's a man-eating plant'un.
Man-eating?!
What is with this place?!
This is the highwayman's forest, Grinston.
H-h-help!!!
Grand Line
Lazy Bones Island Land of
Poverty
I-Is this the Devil?
We really managed to summon him with our black magic!
What a frightening appearance!
He's clearly not of this world...
Our wish can be fulfilled!
We can have our revenge on those people!
We have nothing left!
We will have our revenge on the Longarm tribe, who have taken everything from us!
King of Demons, Satan-sama...
If you will fulfill our wishes,
then every one of us will surrender our very souls to you!
Please rain death upon them!
How far can I have flown?
I have to go back...
Back to where the others are!
Please wait!
Please do not return to Hell, Satan-sama!
We must keep him here, whatever it takes!
Maybe we didn't offer enough sacrifices?
What could Satan-sama want?
Maybe a living sacrifice?
Blood?
Where is this place?
Excuse me...
May I see your panties?
P-Panties!
Hurry and show him your underwear!
East Blue
Country on the bridge
Tequila Wolf
This is a country of laborers.
Pull! Pull!
The people working here are all criminals from other countries,
or inhabitants from countries that
refused to join the World Government.
Stand up! Stand up!
I guess you could call them slaves.
When will this bridge be completed?
It'll probably take a while...
We've been working on it for seven hundred years, after all.
Seven hundred years? What for?
You have no need to know.
You're one of our workers now,
so you just have to build the bridge!
South Blue
What's with these birds?!
They're too big!
You wanna eat me?!
My body's not listening to me!
I'm... safe...?
It's a raccoon dog. How rare!
We having raccoon dog stew.
Stop it! I'm a reindeer!
Then we be having reindeer stew...
Huh? It talk just now?
Legends say that this is a treasure island...
Torino Kingdom where birds reign over humans...
Grand Line Gloom Island
Muggy Kingdom
It's true, I did tell him that...
"If I were to go on a vacation, I'd like to go to a dark, gloomy, haunted old castle...
...where I'd spend my days singing cursed songs."
Damn you, Kuma!
But no one told me there wouldn't be any servants here!
No one told me that I wouldn't get to wake up in a soft bed, being served a bagel sandwich with warm cocoa!
No one told me there wouldn't be any cute stuffed animals here!!!
Where am I? Moria-sama!
I want to go back to Thriller Bark!
Could it be...?
I knew it! Someone else got sent here!
I sure hope it's somebody cute!
H-He's...
...one of Straw Hat's crew!
He must have been defeated by Kuma...
He isn't dead yet?
I'm alive...
Where am I?
What are you doing here?
I should be asking you that!
Crying out all of a sudden...
Where are my swords?
Oh, you want your weapons back?
Why, you...!
Returning to the present...
Luffy intends to help his brother Ace escape,
and is crossing the waves, heading toward Impel Down.
How many times must I repeat myself before you understand?!
You ought to remember it after the first time, you imbecile.
My meals must weigh no less than 100 kilograms!
Any less than that, it will not satisfy my hunger!
Do you wish for me to turn you to stone again?!
N-No! Please forgive me!
I'll be more precise this time!
Someone bring her another meal now!
I-Is that-?
They're examples...
That's what happens to anyone who tries to peek into Hancock's room!
Scary!
Here, Luffy. Dig in!
This is delicious!
And the fact that you're feeding it to me makes the meal even better!
Oh, you don't mean that...
If only that would happen...
Hey, what're you doin' over there in the corner?
You're not eating anything? This Sea King-meat tastes awesome.
I-I am fine...
My heart is already full...
I sure ate a lot!
That was great!
L-Luffy!
Have you forgotten that you are a fugitive?
Hancock! Do you have someone else in your room?
Oh, no!
Lieutenant Stalker, are you sure about what you heard?
Yessir! I definitely heard someone say "Bwah! I sure ate a lot"!
Do you really think the empress would say something like that?
No way!
If that was her, then I'll shave my hair into a Mohawk!
I sure ate a lot!
She said it!
Please remove the dishes.
The meal was satisfying.
Do not forget, I need five portions like this every day.
That much?!
But then we won't have anything to eat!
I would not care if you were to die.
You're horrible!
But you're so beautiful~!
Six days remain before Portgas D. Ace's execution.
Whitebeard has eliminated the scouts sent to watch him,
doubling the tension at Navy HQ.
The port of Marineford is now crowded
with well-known, strong marines returning from their outposts all around the world.
All forces who carry the name of "Justice"...
have gathered at Navy HQ.
Meanwhile, in the Holy Land of Mariejoa,
the assembled members of the Seven Warlords
are instructed to form their own battle unit.
It is a gathering of unruly misfits.
There is but one thing that can be said for certain:
The idea of these men fighting together is unthinkable.
Kill you, you say?
Fool!
Anything we could do now would be pointless.
Even if you died right now,
it wouldn't stop Whitebeard.
Nobody can stop this now.
We have angered...
...the king of the sea!
Translation, Yibis
Soundtracking, Halee
Editing, Sewil
Infoboxes/title card, BernieCrane
Timing, Datenshi
Quality checking, Galaxy 9000, alasta, Mr. Luffy